Tufts University Website Collection UA203
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Student organizations web crawls, 2011 -- 2021; UA203.002; 575 Web sites
  - Students for a Just and Stable Future (SJSF) - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000200
  - Taiwanese Association of Students at Tufts - Home, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000201
  - Tasty Tufts, 2015-10-07 -- 2018-03-14; UA203.000202
  - Teach in CORES, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000203
  - Amalgamates, 2017 -- 2020; UA203.000204
  - Baseball Analysts, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000205
  - Crafts Center at Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000206
  - Crafts House at Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2016 -- 2020; UA203.000207; Crafts House
  - The Giving Camp - Home Page, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000208
  - The Ladies of Essence, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000209
  - The Leonard Carmichael Society, 2015-12-09 - 2017-03-09; UA203.000210
  - The Xi Tau Chapter of Delta Sigma Theta Sorority, 2015-10-07 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.000211
  - THFES - Tufts Human Factors and Ergonomics Society, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000212
  - Tom Thumb's Student Garden, 2015 -- 2019; UA203.000213
  - American Chemical Society, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000214; Tufts American Chemical Society
  - Active Minds, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000215
  - African Dance Collective - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000216
  - African Students Organisation - Home | Facebook, 2016 April 11; UA203.000217; African Students Organization
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000218
  - Anime Brigade, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000219
  - Armenian Club, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000220
  - Art History Society - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000221
  - Balance Your Life - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000223
  - Tufts Beats, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000224
  - Tufts Bhangra, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000225
  - Tufts Bikes, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000226
  - Tufts Black Student Union, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000227
  - Tufts CAFE - Twitter, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000228; Tufts CAFÉ
  - Tufts Cannon, 2015-12-09 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.000229
  - Tufts Chapter of Delta Upsilon - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000230
  - Tufts Cheap Sox, 2015-12-09 - 2016-04-11; UA203.000231
  - Tufts Cheese Club - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000232
  - China Care, 2018 -- 2020; UA203.000233
  - China Care - Twitter, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000234
  - Tufts Chinese Students Association - CSA, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000235
  - Climbing Team, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000236
  - Club Tennis, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000237
  - Tufts Community Emergency Response Team, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000238
  - Tufts Community Union, 2015-10-07 -- 2019-08-21; UA203.000239
  - Tufts Computer Science Exchange, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000240
  - Consulting Collective, 2015 -- 2017; UA203.000241
  - CSA/WuZee, 2015 -- 2017; UA203.000242
  - Culinary Society - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000243
  - Tufts Cycling Team, 2015-10-07 -- 2018-03-14; UA203.000244
  - Tufts Cycling Team - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000245
  - Tufts Dance Collective, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000246
  - Tufts Debate Society, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000247
  - Tufts Debate Society - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000248
  - Tufts Democrats, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000249
  - Ears for Peers, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000250
  - Tufts Ears for Peers, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000251
  - Eco Reps - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000252
  - Economics Society, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000253
  - Elections Commission (ECOM) - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000254
  - Tufts Enchanted - Twitter, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000255
  - Tufts' Enchanted A Cappella - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000256; Tufts Enchanted a cappella
  - Tufts Engineering Mentors - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000257
  - Tufts Engineering Mentors Program, 2015 -- 2019; UA203.000258
  - Tufts Engineers Without Borders, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000259
  - Tufts Entrepreneurs Society, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000260
  - Tufts Entrepreneurs Society, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000261
  - Tufts Equestrian, 2020 December 16; UA203.000262
    Frequency: bimonthly crawl.
  - Tufts Ewo, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000263
  - Tufts Film Series, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000264
  - Tufts Financial Group, 2015-10-07 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.000265
  - Tufts FOCUS - Freshman Orientation Community Service, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000266
  - Tufts for Hillary - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000267
  - Tufts Freethought Society, 2015 -- 2017; UA203.000268
  - Tufts Freethought Society - Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000269
  - Tufts Friends of Israel - Tufts Hillel, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000270
  - Tufts Gaming Hub - Home | Facebook, 2017 -- 2020; UA203.000271
  - Tufts Global China Connection, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000272
  - Tufts Graduate Student Council, 2020 November 15; UA203.000274
  - Tufts HerCampus, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000275
  - Tufts Hillel, 2015-10-07 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.000276
  - Tufts Hindu Students Council, 2009-11-09 -- 2015-08-28; UA203.000277
  - Tufts Historical Review, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000278
  - Tufts Hockey Club, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000279
  - Tufts Hong Kong Student Association, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000280
  - Tufts Idea Exchange, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000281
  - Tufts Idea Exchange - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000282
  - Tufts Institute for Political Citizenship, 2015 -- 2017; UA203.000283
  - Tufts Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000284
  - Tufts Jackson Jills, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000285
  - Tufts Japanese Culture Club, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000286
  - Tufts Japanese Culture Club - Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000287
  - Tufts Judicial Advocates - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000288
  - Tufts JumboCast, 2016 -- 2020; UA203.000289
  - Tufts JumboRaas, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000290
  - Tufts Korean Students Association - KSA, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000291
  - Tufts Latin American Committee, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000293
  - Tufts Latter-Day Saints Student Association Home, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000294
  - Tufts LiNK: Liberty in North Korea, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000295
  - Tufts Maker Network, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000296
  - Tufts Maps, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000297; Tufts Minority Association of Pre-Health Students
  - Tufts Math Society, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000298
  - Tufts Men's Club Volleyball - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000299
  - Tufts Men's Fencing, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000300
  - Tufts Men's Rugby Club, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000301
  - Tufts Men's Ultimate, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000302
  - Tufts Middle Eastern Dance, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000303
  - Tufts Minority Association of Pre-Health Students, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000304
  - Tufts Mock Trial, 2017-06-09 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.000305
  - Tufts Model United Nations, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000306
  - Tufts oSTEM, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000307
  - Tufts Pan Afrikan Alliance, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000308
  - Tufts Pan-African Alliance, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000309
  - Tufts Panhellenic Council, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000310
  - Tufts Parnassus, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000311
  - Tufts Parnassus, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000312
  - Tufts Podcast Network, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000313
  - Tufts Podcast Network - Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000314
  - Tufts Podcasters, 2016 -- 2020; UA203.000315
  - Tufts Premedical Society, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000316
  - Tufts Pre-Veterinary Society, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000317
  - Tufts Psychology Society, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000318
  - Tufts Queer Students Association - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000319
  - Tufts Quidditch, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000320
  - Tufts RacEd - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000321
  - Tufts RacEd | Those who know better, do better., 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000322
  - Tufts Robotic Sail Team, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000323
  - Tufts Robotics Club, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000324
  - Tufts Russian and Slavic Student Association, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000325
  - Tufts Shotokan Karate Club, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000326
  - Tufts SIAM, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000327; Tufts Chapter of the Society for Industrial and Applied Mathematics
  - Tufts Singapore Students Association - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000328; Tufts Singapore Students Association
  - Tufts Ski Team, 2015 -- 2019; UA203.000329
  - Tufts Society of Women Engineers, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000330
  - Tufts Stand-up Comedy Collective - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000331
  - Tufts Students for Justice in Palestine, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000332
  - Tufts Students for Sensible Drug Policy, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000333
  - Tufts SURGE - Sino-US Relations Group Engagement, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000334
  - Tufts Sustainability Collective, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000335
  - Tufts Table Tennis Club (TTTC), 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000336
    Frequency: one-time crawl. (Inactive)
  - Tufts Tamasha - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000337
  - Tufts Tap Ensemble, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000338
  - Tufts Thai Students Association, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000339
  - Tufts Theta Chi, Epsilon Theta Chapter, 2015 -- 2017; UA203.000340
  - Tufts Thetas, 2015-10-07 -- 2018-03-14; UA203.000341
  - Tufts Thirst Project, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000342
  - Tufts TIMMY - Tuft's Undergraduate Global Health Network, 2015 -- 2018; UA203.000343
  - Tufts Traveling Treasure Trunk, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000344
  - Tufts TURBO, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000345
  - Tufts Tutoring, 2015-12-09 - 2017-03-09; UA203.000346
  - Tufts UEP Student Planning and Policy Association - Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000347
  - Tufts United for Immigrant Justice - Facebook, 2015-10-07 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.000348
  - Tufts Univeristy Alpha Phi, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000349
  - Tufts Univeristy's Science Fiction and Fantasy Society, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000350
  - Tufts University - Primary Care Progress, 2015 -- 2018; UA203.000351
  - Tufts University Anthropology Collective, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000352
  - Tufts University Chapter of the Biomedical Engineering Society, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000353
  - Tufts University Chorale, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000354
  - Tufts University Concert Board - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000355
  - Tufts University Engineers Without Borders, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000356
  - Tufts University History Society, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000357
  - Tufts University International Club, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000358
  - Tufts University Pre-Dental Society, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000359
  - Tufts University Programming Board, 2016 -- 2020; UA203.000360
  - Tufts University Programming Board - Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000361
  - Tufts University Tae Kwon Do, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000362
  - Tufts University Wind Ensemble, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000363
  - Tufts University Women's Club Soccer - TUWFC - Facebook, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000364
  - Tufts University, Massachusetts MMA: Mixed Martial Arts Classes, Programs, Workouts, Coaching and Personal Training, 2015 -- 2018; UA203.000365
  - Tufts University's Torn Ticket II, 2015 -- 2015; UA203.000366
  - Tufts Urban Policy, Planning, and Prosperity - UP3 - Home | Facebook, 2015 -- 2016; UA203.000367
  - Tufts Vietnamese Students Club, 2015-10-07 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.000368
  - Tufts Vox: Students for Reproductive Justice, 2017 -- 2020; UA203.000369
  - Tufts Water Polo, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000370
  - Tufts Wilderness Orientation, 2015 -- 2017; UA203.000117
    For crawls after March 2016, see students.tufts.edu and navigate to the Orientation page.
  - Tufts Women's Club Volleyball, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000371
  - Tufts Women's Lacrosse - Facebook, 2015-10-07 -- 2016-04-11; UA203.000372
  - Tufts Women's Rugby Football Club, 2015-10-07 -- 2019-05-15; UA203.000373
  - Tufts Zeta Beta Tau, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000374
  - WMFO, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000375
  - ACM-W Tufts Chapter, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000379; Association for Computing Machinery-Women Tufts Chapter; 1 Web sites
  - ALLIES, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000380; 1 Web sites
  - Athletes of Color at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000381; Athletes of Color at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Biomechanics at Tufts – Club & Research, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000382; Biomechanics at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Biomedical Engineering and Chemical Engineering Society, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000383; 1 Web sites
  - Chabad Serving Tufts University, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000384; 1 Web sites
  - Civil and Environmental Engineering Graduate Student Organization, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000385; 1 Web sites
  - COCOA Dancers - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000386; COCOA Dancers; 1 Web sites
  - College Diabetes Network, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000387; 1 Web sites
  - Computer Science League of Learning, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000388; 1 Web sites
  - Currents Magazine - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000389; Currents Magazine; 1 Web sites
  - Department of English: Graduate, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000390; Department of English; 1 Web sites
  - Design for Social Good at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000391; Design for Social Good at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - ESA, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000392; European Student Association; 1 Web sites
  - First-Generation Students at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000393; First-Generation Students at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Gamma Chapter of The Omega Psi Phi Fraternity - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000394; Gamma Chapter of The Omega Psi Phi Fraternity; 1 Web sites
  - iGem, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000395; Tufts iGEM; 1 Web sites
  - Institute Sketch Comedy - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000396; 1 Web sites
  - Jumbo Jugglers - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000397; 1 Web sites
  - JumboCode, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000398; 1 Web sites
  - La Société française - Tufts French Society - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000400; Tufts French Society; 1 Web sites
  - Left Unity Project - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000401; The Left Unity Project; 1 Web sites
  - Lord Barnum's Players, 2019-12-06; UA203.000402; 1 Web sites
  - Peer Education - CARE, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000403; 1 Web sites
  - Pen Paint & Pretzels, 2015 -- 2020; UA203.000404; Pen, Paint and Pretzels; 1 Web sites
  - Petey Greene Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000405; Petey Greene Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - PIH Engage | Partners In Health, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000406; PIH Engage; 1 Web sites
  - Public Harmony - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000407; 1 Web sites
  - Roots - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000408; Roots; 1 Web sites
  - ROTI and RUM - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000409; 1 Web sites
  - SMFA Student Government Association - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000410; 1 Web sites
  - Spirit of the Creative - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000411; Spirit of the Creative; 1 Web sites
  - Students for Environmental Awareness -SEA - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000412; Students for Environmental Awareness; 1 Web sites
  - TAMID at Tufts | Home, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000413; TAMID at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Tasty Tufts, 2018 -- 2020; UA203.000414; 1 Web sites
  - TFL COMEDY, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000415; TFL Comedy; 1 Web sites
  - ACLU - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000416; Tufts ACLU; 1 Web sites
  - Animal Welfare – Student-Run Organization Involved in Campus Education and Community Outreach, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000417; Tufts Animal Welfare; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Arab Student Association - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000418; 1 Web sites
  - American Society of Civil Engineers, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000419; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Asian Student Coalition - TASC - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000420; 1 Web sites
  - Association of South Asians - Home - Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000421; 1 Web sites
  - Black Students in Computer Science, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000422; Tufts Black Students in Computer Science; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Blockchain Club, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000423; 1 Web sites
  - Brazilian Student Association - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000424; Brazilian Student Association; 1 Web sites
  - Burlesque Troupe - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000425; Tufts Burlesque Troupe; 1 Web sites
  - Cape Verdean Student Association - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000426; Tufts Cape Verdean Student Association; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Child Development Association - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000427; Tufts Child Development Association; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts CIVIC, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000428; 1 Web sites
  - Climate Action - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000429; Tufts Climate Action; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Community Union, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000430; 1 Web sites
  - Country Swing Dance Public Group | Home - Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000431; Tufts Country Swing Dance; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Cricket Club - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000432; Tufts University Cricket Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Cycling Team, 2018 -- 2020; UA203.000433; 1 Web sites
  - Electric Racing, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000435; Tufts Electric Racing; 1 Web sites
  - Encendido - Home | Facebook - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000436; Tufts Encendido; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Energy Group - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000437; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Filipinx Student Union - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000438; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts German Club - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000439; Tufts German Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Italian Club - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000441; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Lifting Club - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000443; Tufts Lifting Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts MAKE - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000444; Tufts MAKE; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Neuronetwork, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000445; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Peace Action - Home, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000446; Tufts Peace Action; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Pep Band - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000447; Tufts Pep Band; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Persian Student Association - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000448; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Progressive Alliance - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000449; Tufts Progressive Alliance; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Real Estate, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000450; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Returning Students Organization - Home | Facebook, 2018 -- 2020; UA203.000451; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts SEDS – Tufts University SEDS Chapter, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000452; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts sQ! – Tufts' Freshest All-Gender A Cappella Group, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000453; Tufts sQ!; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts STOMP | Student Teacher Outreach Mentorship Program, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000454; Tufts STOMP; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Student Action - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000455; Tufts Student Action; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Students for NARAL - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000456; Tufts Students for NARAL; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts SWE, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000457; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Tabletop Gaming Club 2019-2020 - Home | Facebook, UA203.000458; Tufts Tabletop Gaming Club; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Thetas, 2018 -- 2020; UA203.000459; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Chaplaincy, 2015-12-09 -- 2019-11-15; UA203.000460; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts University Republicans, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000461; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Women's Rugby Football Club - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000462; 1 Web sites
  - WiCS - Women in Computer Science, 2019-12-06; UA203.000463; 1 Web sites
  - Women Entrepreneurs @ Tufts, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000464; Women Entrepreneurs at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Women Entrepreneurs at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2019-12-06; UA203.000465; 1 Web sites
  - Full Sound Vocal Group - Home | Facebook, 2019 -- 2020; UA203.000466; Full Sound Vocal Group; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts | Colleges Occupy Boston, 2011-11-07; UA203.000570; 1 Web sites
  - Tufts Occupiers - Wall | Facebook, 2011-11-07; UA203.000571; 1 Web sites
  - ABLE: Access Betters the Lives of Everyone - Instagram, 2020 -- 2021; UA203.000572; ABLE: Access Betters the Lives of Everyone; 1 Web sites
  - About ECOM — Tufts Community Union, 2020 December 16; UA203.000573; Tufts Community Union Election Commission; 1 Web sites
  - About Senate — Tufts Community Union, 2020 December 16; UA203.000574; Tufts Community Union Senate; 1 Web sites
  - About The J — Tufts Community Union, 2020 December 16; UA203.000575; Tufts Community Union Judiciary; 1 Web sites
  - ACTION (Advancing Civic Thought in Our Nation), 2020 December 16; UA203.000576; Tufts ACTION; 1 Web sites
  - Action for Sexual Assault Prevention at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000577; Action for Sexual Assault Prevention at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Action for Sexual Assault Prevention at Tufts - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000578; Action for Sexual Assault Prevention at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Active Minds at Tufts, 2020 December 16; UA203.000579; 1 Web sites
  - Active Minds at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000580; Active Minds at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - AIChE Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000581; AIChE Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - ALLIES - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000582; ALLIES: Alliance Linking Leaders in Education and the Services; 1 Web sites
  - Alpha Phi at Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000583; Alpha Phi, Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - American Institute of Chemical Engineers - Tufts University Student Chapter, 2020 November 15; UA203.000584; American Institute of Chemical Engineers Chapter at Tufts; 1 Web sites
  - Applejam Productions - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000585; Applejam Productions; 1 Web sites
  - Arab Student Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000586; Arab Student Association; 1 Web sites
  - Artists of Color Union at SMFA - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000587; Artists of Color Union at SMFA; 1 Web sites
  - Asian Student Coalition - TASC - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000588; Tufts Asian Student Coalition; 1 Web sites
  - Association of Latin American Students at Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000589; Association of Latin American Students; 1 Web sites
  - Black Student Union - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000590; Tufts Black Student Union; 1 Web sites
  - BlackOut Step Team - Twitter, 2020 December 16; UA203.000591; BlackOut Step Team; 1 Web sites
  - Boxers on the Hill - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000592; Boxers on the Hill; 1 Web sites
  - Breakthrough: Tufts Undergraduate Science Magazine, 2020 November 15; UA203.000593; Office for Campus Life; 1 Web sites
  - Chabad Serving Tufts - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000594; Chabad Serving Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - Cheap Sox - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000595; Cheap Sox; 1 Web sites
  - Chinese Students Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 November 15; UA203.000596; Tufts Chinese Students Association; 1 Web sites
  - COFFEE Tufts Interfaith Student - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000597; COFFEE Tufts Interfaith Student Coalition; 1 Web sites
  - Computer Science Exchange, 2020 November 15; UA203.000598; Tufts Computer Science Exchange; 1 Web sites
  - EMS - AID at Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000599; Essential Medical Supplies and Activism for Inequities and Disasters at Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - European Horizons | Tufts Global Leadership, 2020 December 16; UA203.000600; European Horizons at Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - European Horizons at Tufts University - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000601; European Horizons at Tufts University; 1 Web sites
  - European Students' Association - Home | Facebook, 2020 -- 2020; UA203.000602; European Student Association; 1 Web sites